777score.com 2019-05-31

# 777score

### 1 Terms of Use

These Terms of Use (hereafter referred to as the ‘ToU’) constitute and govern the relationship between ‘Provider’ (defined below) and all parties who access the websites and/or mobile applications (defined hereunder) and make use of their features and contents in any manner (hereafter referred to as ‘Visitors’).

Collectively the Provider and the Visitors shall be referred to as the ‘Parties’.

### 2 General

The use of any or all of the features and services offered by the Provider on mobile applications and websites 777score.co.uk 777score.cm 777score.mu 777score.ng 777score.in 777score.ke 777score.pk 777score.ph 777score.nz 777score.kz 777score.ru 777score.ua skorexpress.com 777score.com 777score.com.br. (hereafter referred to as the ‘Site’) and the information materials and links contained therein is subject to the ToU as set out below. Unless otherwise agreed by the Provider in writing the ToU constitute the entire relationship between the Provider and the Visitor in its use of the Site including any or all of its functions on offer by the Site.

The Visitor has the duty to read carefully and understand the ToU before using the Site. A Visitor who has viewed the Site is considered to have read understood and agreed to be bound by the ToU without the need for any further act.

The Provider hereby reserves the right to suspend add end amend and/or supplement these ToU from time to time as it may deem appropriate.

The Provider recommends that the Visitor reads carefully the contents of these pages regularly. By using the Site the Visitor agrees to be bound by the ToU as well as by the latest modifications to them regardless of whether in fact the Visitor is aware of such modifications.

The Provider is under no obligation to verify that all Visitors use the Site according to the last updated ToU. The effective version of ToU is that which is posted on the Site.

The Site may only be used for lawful purposes. Use of the Site for transmission distribution publication or storage of any material on or via the Site which is in violation of any applicable law or regulation or any third party's rights is strictly prohibited. This includes (without limitation) the use of the Site or the transmission distribution publication or storage of any material on or via the Site in a matter or for a purpose which infringes copyright trademark trade secret or other intellectual property rights is obscene or harmful to minors or constitutes an illegal act or harassment is libellous or defamatory violates any privacy or data protection laws is fraudulent or breaches any exchange control or gambling law.

In the event of misuse and/or the abuse of the Site the Provider reserves the right to close or block the Visitor from the Site and close any account registered in the Visitor’s name. The Provider retains the right to bring a lawsuit against the Visitor and at its sole discretion.

### 3 Services

The Site provides an interactive web and/or mobile application/features containing live sports information in sporting events sports scores in real time final results fixtures line ups and sports statistics. The results and other statistics information contained on the Site reflect information provided by other independent sources (from third parties) or by in-house effort or by various other official Sites. While every effort is made by the Provider to update the content and match results or other information displayed on the Site regularly we advise to double check information gathered on Site also from other sources. The Provider is not responsible for the Visitor’s use of the results and other information contained on the Site.

### 4 Third party Websites and Apps

The Visitor acknowledges that any contact whatsoever made with third parties after viewing the Site whether intended or unintended and any outcome which ensues is absolutely independent of the Provider and the Provider is not in any way responsible for any agreement or expectation and other consequence which ensues as a direct or indirect cause of this contact.

Any claim or dispute which may arise between the Visitor and such a third party shall in no way involve the Provider.

Third parties including any third parties advertising on the Site do not have access to the Visitors’ Personal Data and any other data that the Visitor may have given to the Provider.

### 5 A/V Content

The Provider is not responsible for the content of external Sites which may be viewed from the Site. All video content found on the Site is not hosted on the Provider’s servers nor is it created or uploaded to the host server by the Provider.

### 6 Inactive Accounts

If a Visitor has set up an account on the Site but fails to access it for 60 days the Provider reserves the right to close the account with immediate effect and without prior notice.

### 7 Intellectual Property

Without prior authorisation in writing from the Provider Visitors are not authorised to copy modify tamper with distribute transmit display reproduce transfer upload download or otherwise use or alter any of the content of the Site.

777Score is registered trademark and is used by Sport Labs Group Limited under license agreement.

Any breach of this clause may be tantamount to a violation of applicable intellectual property rights within the European Union and other applicable laws. The Provider and any other party authorised on its behalf reserves the right to seek damages to the fullest extent permitted by law against any party committing directly or indirectly this breach.

### 8 Type of Relationship

These ToU are not intended to create any partnership agency or joint venture between the Provider and the Visitor.

### 9 Breach of ToU

If the Visitor fails to adhere to any clause in the ToU or if the Provider reasonably suspects that a Visitor whether directly or indirectly fails to comply with any clause in the ToU the Provider reserves the right and all remedies at its disposition and at its sole discretion to close or block the Visitor from the Site and close any account registered in the Visitor’s name and related to it and retains the right to bring a lawsuit against the Visitor at its sole discretion.

### 10 Legal Compliance

Visitors are advised to comply with applicable legislation in the jurisdiction in which they are domiciled and/or resident and/or present. The Provider does not accept responsibility for any action taken by any authority against any Visitor in connection with their use of the Site.

### 11 Law & Forum and/or community

These ToU shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the country of Malta without giving effect to conflicts of law principles. The Parties submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the court of the country of Malta for the settlement of any disputes arising out of or concerning these ToU. These ToU will not be governed by the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods the application of which is expressly excluded.

### 12 Headings

Headings are intended for clarity and to facilitate reading of these ToU. They are not intended as a means of interpretation for the content of the paragraph that follows each heading. Headings are not intended to bind the Provider in any manner whatsoever.

### 13 Waiver

Any waiver by the Provider of any breach by any Visitor of any provision of these ToU shall not be considered as a waiver of any subsequent breach of the same or any other provision of these ToU.

### 14 Disclaimer

### 14.1 Warranties and Representations

It is hereby being specified that the Provider makes no representation pledge or warranty (either explicit or implicit) that the content of the Site is accurate and/or suitable for any particular purpose other than those warranties which cannot be expressly excluded under the governing law of these ToU.

Use of the Site is entirely at the Visitor’s risk. The Site is not a gaming or gambling Site. The Provider of the Site does not provide gaming or gambling services; therefore it does not hold or control player funds and it is not involved in any gaming transactions. Betting odds which are displayed on the Site are part of information and functions of the Site.

The Provider does not guarantee that:- any of the functions provided by the Site are authorised that the operation will fully satisfy the Visitor that it is entirely secure and exempt from error that it is updated regularly that any software defect is regularly corrected that it is uninterrupted that the Site are virus or bug free that they are continually operational that they are adequate that the information and functions available thereon is reliable or that all other information obtained and functions used on the Site are adequate and reliable. Those who choose to access the Site do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws if and to the extent local laws are applicable.

The Site may contain links and references to third party websites/apps/adverts/content. Those other websites/apps/adverts/content will be subject to separate terms and conditions normally contained in those websites/apps/adverts/content. These are provided for the convenience and interest of the Visitor and does not imply responsibility for nor approval of information contained in these websites/apps/adverts/content by the Provider. The Provider gives no warranty either expressed or implied as to the accuracy availability of content or information text or graphics which are not under its domain. The Provider has not tested any software located on other websites/apps and does not make any representation as to the quality safety reliability or suitability of such software.

### 15 Privacy Policy

The website 777score (herein referred to as the ‘Site’) respects the privacy of all parties viewing and otherwise making use of the Site (herein referred to as the <span>‘Visitors’</span>) and is committed to protecting their privacy. The Site may collect and use ‘Personal Data’ (defined hereunder) relating to its Visitors in order to provide them with the services provided by the Site and only for any purpose which has been expressly stated hereunder.

This Privacy Policy complies with international Conventions and EU laws including the General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/679) as transposed into Maltese law in Data Protection Act (Chapter 440 of the laws of Malta) the Processing of Personal Data (Electronic Communications Sector) Regulations (Legal Notice 16 of 2003 inclusive of the later amendments) it adopts Recommendation 2/2001 of the Article 29 Data Protection Working Party adopted on 17 May 2001 on certain minimum requirements for collecting personal data on-line and implements also any other Sitelicable rules and practices.

The Controller of data collected and used from Visitors of the Site is Sport Labs Group Limited registered office: 35 Strait Street Valletta VLT 1432 Malta and is responsible for this Site.

The Data Controller can be contacted on gdpr@777score.com.

The Provider can be contacted on gdpr@777score.com.

### 16 Purpose of this Statement

The purpose of this Statement is to:

● set out the type of personal data the Controller will collect from you and how we will use your personal information;

● the basis on which any personal data is processed by the Controller;

● make you aware of how the Controller will handle your personal data;

● clarify the Controller’s obligations under the data protection regulations with regards to processing your personal data lawfully and responsibly; and

● inform you of your data protection rights.

We process your personal data in an appropriate and lawful manner in accordance with applicable data protection regulations and the General Data Protection Regulation EU 2016/679 (the “GDPR”) which is in force as of 25 May 2018.

### 17 Collection of Personal Data

Save where specifically indicated in this Privacy Policy the Site does not collect any Personal Data when Visitors simply browse the Site. However the Site does require that Visitors supply some Personal Data when using additional or advanced services provided on the Site after the registration. On these occasions the Site will ask Visitors for their respective consent prior to the collection and use of the Visitors’ Personal Data. Upon registration or at other times the Site may ask Visitors to submit their login name (an e-mail address typically) and password.

Visitors are under no obligation to provide their Personal Data or to permit their Personal Data to be collected by the Site. However the Site may not be able to provide the Visitors not consenting to the collection of their Personal Data with all services offered by the Site.

Although Visitors may have consented to the Site using their respective Personal Data they are entitled to subsequently revoke their respective consent for whatever reason by contacting gdpr@777score.com. In case of revocation of consent the additional or advance services provided on the Site after registration will no longer be available.

### 18 Your Rights as a Data Subject

### 18.1.1 The Right of Access

Visitors are entitled to request that the Controller (defined hereafter) provides them with written information on which of their respective Personal Data it has collected and/or used. A request can be made by submitting a request in writing to the Controller (defined hereafter).

The Site undertakes to make all reasonable efforts to keep the Personal Data collected updated. However Visitors are invited to inform the Site of any changes to their Personal Data which is held by the Site.

### 18.1.2 Correction Blocking or Deletion of Data

Visitors who consider that any of their respective Personal Data is inaccurate may request the Controller in writing to correct the data. Visitors also have the right to request the Controller to block or delete their respective Personal Data if it has been processed unlawfully.

### 18.1.3 Right to object

You may contact us at any time at gdpr@777score.com to ask us not to process your Personal Data for marketing purposes e.g. receiving information from us about upcoming events newsletters and publications and your data will no longer be processed for such purposes.

### 18.1.4 Right to withdraw consent

You have the right to withdraw your consent to this statement and the processing practices described herein at any time by sending an email to gdpr@777score.com. This will not affect the lawfulness of processing which we carried out on the basis of such consent before its withdrawal. Withdrawal of consent will result in us having to terminate our services immediately.

### 18.1.5 Right to rectification

You have the right to obtain rectification of any inaccurate Personal Data about you that we have processed update any data which is out-of-date and the right to have incomplete Personal Data completed including by means of a supplementary statement.

### 18.1.6 Right to erasure

You have the right to obtain the erasure of Personal Data we have concerning you when your personal data is no longer required where:

● you withdraw your consent to us processing your Personal Data;

● your Personal Data no longer needs to be processed; or

● your Personal Data has been unlawfully processed.

### 18.1.7 Right to Restriction of Processing

You have the right to restrict our processing activities where:

● you consent the accuracy of this Personal Data for a period enabling us to verify the accuracy of the same Personal Data;

● our processing is deemed unlawful and you oppose the erasure of your Personal Data and request restriction of its use instead;

● we no longer need your Personal Data for the purposes stated herein but you require it for the establishment exercising or defending of legal claims; or

● you have objected to our processing pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of our processing activities overrode those pertaining to you.

### 18.1.8 Right of Data Portability

As from 25 May 2018 you shall have the right to receive your Personal Data in a structured and machine-readable format and transmit this data to another Controller (as defined in the GDPR).

### 19 Purposes for the collection and use of Personal Data

The Personal Data collected by the Site shall be processed in accordance with the provisions of the Data Protection Act (Chapter 440 of the Laws of Malta) and subsidiary legislation enacted thereunder and solely processed for the purposes of:

  1. Communicating with the Visitors;

  2. Sending Visitors new password to their respective personal account;

  3. Providing any advanced services which are possible to configure Site to some extent;

  4. Improving the content offered by the Site;

  5. Providing Visitors with personalised Site content and/or layout.

### 20 Legal basis for processing

We shall only process your Personal Data where you have provided your consent or insofar as this is necessary for us to be able to provide the services we offer and/or for the purposes indicated in this statement.

We may also process your Personal Data on the basis of any legitimate interest or in order to comply with any legal obligations at law. This may include the exercise of defense of legal claims or in order to comply with an order of any court tribunal or authority.

### 21 Marketing

You will receive marketing communication from us if you have requested such marketing information from us by providing us with your details through this Site and have opted-in to receiving such information.

We will not share your Personal Data with any third party for marketing purposes without your unambiguous consent.

### 22 Disclosure of Personal Data to third parties

The Provider does not sell trade or rent or otherwise disclose Personal Data appertaining to Visitors to any third party without their prior respective consent. However Personal Data would be disclosed to third parties in the eventuality of a sale of the Site.

The above is without prejudice to any legal obligation incumbent on the Site to disclose Visitors’ Personal Data to third parties.

The above is also without prejudice to disclosures which are absolutely necessary as part of one or more of the Purposes for collecting and using Personal Data. In this case the Site shall seek the prior express consent of the Visitors concerned.

The Provider reserves the right to provide statistics about Visitors sales traffic and other statistical information relating to the Site to third parties however without identifying any particular Visitor.

### 23 Log Files

In order to better administer the Site and to collect broad demographic information of Visitors for aggregate use the Site automatically logs the IP address of all Visitors and the pages viewed by each Visitor respectively.

### 24 Cookie Disclaimer

A 'cookie' is information stored on a Visitor’s computer by a web server and used to customise their web service. The Site uses cookies to store information about Visitors’ interactions that may be needed later to perform a function. Visitors can choose to disable cookies in browser settings. We use cookies to personalise content and ads to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our Site analytics partners some advertising partners (programmatic) and social media (only when you log in via your social account).

This statement should be read in conjunction with our Cookie Policy and any other <span>Privacy Notice</span> we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing Personal Data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your Personal Data.

### 25 Transfers of Personal Data to Third Countries

The Controller does not transfer any Personal Data outside the European Economic Area and if it is required to it will first ensure that there are appropriate safeguards in place to ensure that your Personal Data is adequately protected.

### 26 Security

The Site and the Controller have adopted various measures both technical and organisational to help protect communication against the destruction loss misuse and alteration of Personal Data which has been collected and used (including ensuring that any transfers of data are secured) through Secured communication between Visitor's device and Provider's servers “HTTPS”. Additionally all passwords you set up are stored using BCrypt standard. Notwithstanding these efforts the Provider cannot guarantee that such event will not occur.

### 27 The period for which Personal Data is kept

The Personal Data is kept only for the time period required to meet the purposes for which it was collected. In case of user account inactivity for one (1) year all collected user Personal Data will be deleted.

### 28 Third party websites/apps

Third party websites/apps are not covered by this Privacy Policy. The Site provides links to other sites for the convenience of Visitors. The Site is not responsible for the contents displayed on third party websites/apps and measures they adopt to protect your privacy. Any other websites/apps which Visitors access from the Site may not have an adequate Privacy Policy.

### 29 Acceptance of the Privacy Policy

The Visitors’ consent to the collection and use of their respective Personal Data by the Site and the Controller is made subject to the Privacy Policy set out above. Visitors are advised to view the Privacy Policy on a regular basis in order to become familiar with the terms and clauses therein and with any amendments which from time to time may be implemented by the Site.

### 30 Provider

The Provider is Sport Labs Group Limited a company duly registered under the laws of Malta on the 24.08.2018 and having its registered address at 35 Strait Street Valletta VLT 1432 Malta. To contact us please email us at info@777score.com.

### 31 Version and Date of ToU

This statement in version 1 was last updated in 24.08.2018.
